<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Fairese Technologies</title>
    <link>https://www.fairese.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Fairese Technologies</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2019 15:26:26 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.fairese.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Next Anime Episode Privacy Policy</title>
      <link>https://www.fairese.com/privacy-policies/next-anime-episode/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2019 15:26:26 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.fairese.com/privacy-policies/next-anime-episode/</guid>
      <description>Andy Ibanez K built the Next Anime Episode app as a Commercial app. This SERVICE is provided by Andy Ibanez K and is intended for use as is.
This page is used to inform visitors regarding my policies with the collection, use, and disclosure of Personal Information if anyone decided to use my Service.
If you choose to use my Service, then you agree to the collection and use of information in relation to this policy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Next Anime Episode</title>
      <link>https://www.fairese.com/projects/next-anime-episode/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2019 15:23:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.fairese.com/projects/next-anime-episode/</guid>
      <description>Download on the App Store | Privacy Policy
Next Anime Episode does one job: To help you keep track of airing anime and when they will have a new episode available in Japan.
Generally, sub based simulcast streaming services have the newest episodes available within one hour after they air in Japan.
Simply browse the currently airing chart, select which anime you are interested in, and you will receive a notification when a new episode for your selected series is available.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>https://www.fairese.com/portfolio/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2019 15:22:11 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.fairese.com/portfolio/</guid>
      <description>This is a list of our in-house projects:
 Next Anime Episode  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact Us</title>
      <link>https://www.fairese.com/contact-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2019 15:11:42 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.fairese.com/contact-us/</guid>
      <description>If you are having problems with our apps or want to contact us for business purposes, send an e-mail to the following address:
support[at]fairese[dot]com
We try to reply everything within 24 hours.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Us</title>
      <link>https://www.fairese.com/about-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2019 14:51:16 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.fairese.com/about-us/</guid>
      <description>Fairese Technologies is a company focused on iOS App Development. Born in La Paz, Bolivia, we create various entertainment related apps.
Fairese Technologies was born in La Paz, Bolivia, in 2013, after a failed entrepreneurship focused on marketing. We started building our own anime apps, as well as apps for clients. Currently, we plan to expand our own app portfolio to other apps, while always staying true to our initial identity.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>